{
  "reference_number": "9573",
  "clauses": [
    {
      "question": "1. What process should the Government use to set a new emissions reduction target in legislation?",
      "question_index": 0,
      "answer": null,
      "answer_index": 5,
      "notes": "Man made climate change & the Science is UNPROVEN. No action needs to be or should be taken. No emission targets regulated will\n make any difference to the worlds climate which will change naturally through many other factors outside of mans control, so this is a\n\n waste of time, money, expense & any BS tax collected as a consequence should be put to better use, ie Healthcare. This\n survey/submission is also BS as there is no option for the realists to state that this contrivance about man being responsible for the\n changing weather is all a gross political manipulation."
    },
    {
      "question": "2. If the Government sets a 2050 target now, which is the best target for New Zealand?",
      "question_index": 1,
      "answer": null,
      "answer_index": 5,
      "notes": "Man made climate change & the Science is UNPROVEN. No action needs to be or should be taken. No emission targets regulated will\n make any difference to the worlds climate which will change naturally through many other factors outside of mans control, so this is a\n\n waste of time, money, expense & any BS tax collected as a consequence should be put to better use, ie Healthcare. This\n survey/submission is also BS as there is no option for the realists to state that this contrivance about man being responsible for the\n changing weather is all a gross political manipulation."
    },
    {
      "question": "3. How should New Zealand meet its targets?",
      "question_index": 2,
      "answer": null,
      "answer_index": 5,
      "notes": "Man made climate change & the Science is UNPROVEN. No action needs to be or should be taken. No emission targets regulated will\n make any difference to the worlds climate which will change naturally through many other factors outside of mans control, so this is a\n waste of time, money, expense & any BS tax collected as a consequence should be put to better use, ie Healthcare. This\n\n survey/submission is also BS as there is no option for the realists to state that this contrivance about man being responsible for the\n changing weather is all a gross political manipulation."
    },
    {
      "question": "4. Should the Zero Carbon Bill allow the 2050 target to be revised if circumstances change?",
      "question_index": 3,
      "answer": "Yes",
      "answer_index": 3,
      "notes": "Downwards, or completely repealed or abolished since man made climate change & the Science is UNPROVEN. No action needs to\n\n be or should be taken. No emission targets regulated will make any difference to the worlds climate which will change naturally\n through many other factors outside of mans control, so this is a waste of time, money, expense & any BS tax collected as a\n consequence should be put to better use, ie Healthcare. This survey/submission is also BS as there is no option for the realists to\n\n state that this contrivance about man being responsible for the changing weather is all a gross political manipulation."
    },
    {
      "question": "5. The Government proposes that three emissions budgets of five years each (i.e. covering the next 15 years) be in place at any given time. Do you agree with this proposal?",
      "question_index": 15,
      "answer": "No",
      "answer_index": 8,
      "notes": "Man made climate change & the Science is UNPROVEN. No action needs to be or should be taken. No emission targets regulated will\n\n make any difference to the worlds climate which will change naturally through many other factors outside of mans control, so this is a\n waste of time, money, expense & any BS tax collected as a consequence should be put to better use, ie Healthcare. This\n survey/submission is also BS as there is no option for the realists to state that this contrivance about man being responsible for the\n\n changing weather is all a gross political manipulation."
    },
    {
      "question": "6. Should the Government be able to alter the last emissions budget (i.e. furthest into the future)?",
      "question_index": 4,
      "answer": "Yes - each incoming Government should have the option to review the third budget in the sequence",
      "answer_index": 14,
      "notes": "Man made climate change & the Science is UNPROVEN. No action needs to be or should be taken. No emission targets regulated will\n\nmake any difference to the worlds climate which will change naturally through many other factors outside of mans control, so this is a\nwaste of time, money, expense & any BS tax collected as a consequence should be put to better use, ie Healthcare. This\nsurvey/submission is also BS as there is no option for the realists to state that this contrivance about man being responsible for the\n\nchanging weather is all a gross political manipulation."
    },
    {
      "question": "7. Should the Government have the ability to review and adjust the second emissions budget within a specific range under exceptional circumstances? See p36 Our Climate Your Say",
      "question_index": 5,
      "answer": "Yes",
      "answer_index": 3,
      "notes": "Man made climate change & the Science is UNPROVEN. No action needs to be or should be taken. No emission targets regulated will\nmake any difference to the worlds climate which will change naturally through many other factors outside of mans control, so this is a\n\nwaste of time, money, expense & any BS tax collected as a consequence should be put to better use, ie Healthcare. This\nsurvey/submission is also BS as there is no option for the realists to state that this contrivance about man being responsible for the\n\nchanging weather is all a gross political manipulation."
    },
    {
      "question": "8. Do you agree with the considerations we propose that the Government and the Climate Change Commission take into account when advising on and setting budgets? See p44 Our Climate Your Say",
      "question_index": 6,
      "answer": null,
      "answer_index": 5,
      "notes": "Man made climate change & the Science is UNPROVEN. No action needs to be or should be taken. No emission targets regulated will\nmake any difference to the worlds climate which will change naturally through many other factors outside of mans control, so this is a\nwaste of time, money, expense & any BS tax collected as a consequence should be put to better use, ie Healthcare. This\n\nsurvey/submission is also BS as there is no option for the realists to state that this contrivance about man being responsible for the\nchanging weather is all a gross political manipulation."
    },
    {
      "question": "9. Should the Zero Carbon Bill require Governments to set out plans within a certain timeframe to achieve the emissions budgets?",
      "question_index": 7,
      "answer": "No",
      "answer_index": 8,
      "notes": "Man made climate change & the Science is UNPROVEN. No action needs to be or should be taken. No emission targets regulated will\nmake any difference to the worlds climate which will change naturally through many other factors outside of mans control, so this is a\n\nwaste of time, money, expense & any BS tax collected as a consequence should be put to better use, ie Healthcare. This\nsurvey/submission is also BS as there is no option for the realists to state that this contrivance about man being responsible for the\n\nchanging weather is all a gross political manipulation."
    },
    {
      "question": "10. What are the most important issues for the Government to consider in setting plans to meet budgets? For example, who do we need to work with, what else needs to be considered?",
      "question_index": 8,
      "answer": null,
      "answer_index": 5,
      "notes": "Perhaps look at the realistic truth and not the manipulated, brainwashed self interested scientists that incidentally do not form 97%\nconsensus agreement. More manipulated media hyped BS"
    },
    {
      "question": "11. The Government has proposed that the Climate Change Commission advises on and monitors New Zealand's progress towards its goals. Do you agree with these functions? See p42 Our Climate Your Say",
      "question_index": 9,
      "answer": "No",
      "answer_index": 8,
      "notes": "Man made climate change & the Science is UNPROVEN. No action needs to be or should be taken. No emission targets regulated will\nmake any difference to the worlds climate which will change naturally through many other factors outside of mans control, so this is a\n\nwaste of time, money, expense & any BS tax collected as a consequence should be put to better use, ie Healthcare. This\nsurvey/submission is also BS as there is no option for the realists to state that this contrivance about man being responsible for the\n\nchanging weather is all a gross political manipulation."
    },
    {
      "question": "12. What role do you think the Climate Change Commission should have in relation to the New Zealand Emissions Trading Scheme (NZ ETS)?",
      "question_index": 10,
      "answer": null,
      "answer_index": 5,
      "notes": "None. It should be abolished"
    },
    {
      "question": "13. The Government has proposed that Climate Change Commissioners need to have a range of essential and desirable expertise. Do you agree with the proposed expertise? See p45 Our Climate Your Say",
      "question_index": 11,
      "answer": "No",
      "answer_index": 8,
      "notes": "How you can be an expert on something that is untruthful?"
    },
    {
      "question": "14. Do you think the Zero Carbon Bill should cover adapting to climate change?",
      "question_index": 12,
      "answer": "No",
      "answer_index": 8,
      "notes": "Man made climate change & the Science is UNPROVEN. No action needs to be or should be taken. No emission targets regulated will\n\nmake any difference to the worlds climate which will change naturally through many other factors outside of mans control, so this is a\nwaste of time, money, expense & any BS tax collected as a consequence should be put to better use, ie Healthcare. This\n\nsurvey/submission is also BS as there is no option for the realists to state that this contrivance about man being responsible for the\nchanging weather is all a gross political manipulation."
    },
    {
      "question": "15. The Government has proposed a number of new functions to help us adapt to climate change. Do you agree with the proposed functions? See p47 Our Climate Your Say",
      "question_index": 13,
      "answer": "No",
      "answer_index": 8,
      "notes": "Man made climate change & the Science is UNPROVEN. No action needs to be or should be taken. No emission targets regulated will\nmake any difference to the worlds climate which will change naturally through many other factors outside of mans control, so this is a\n\nwaste of time, money, expense & any BS tax collected as a consequence should be put to better use, ie Healthcare. This\nsurvey/submission is also BS as there is no option for the realists to state that this contrivance about man being responsible for the\n\nchanging weather is all a gross political manipulation."
    },
    {
      "question": "16. Should we explore setting up a targeted adaptation reporting power that could see some organisations share information on their exposure to climate change risks?",
      "question_index": 14,
      "answer": "No",
      "answer_index": 8,
      "notes": "What? And waste even more precious financial resources on an issue that won’t be stopped by the worlds population. No more gravy\ntrains needed. This country is already stuffed with this climate change BS rehetoric, and we don’t need any more regulatory BS\ncontrolling groups/committees or otherwise to bleed the average consumer or resident dry of their wealth (what little they have left\n\nafter this Government is finished with them)"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you have any other comments you'd like to make?",
      "question_index": 16,
      "answer": null,
      "answer_index": 5,
      "notes": "I do NOT give consent for my name nor this submission or any parts of this submission to be published in any article, newspaper, or\nother printed publication or made public on any website."
    }
  ]
}
